だが… まさかだよな｡
こんな だだっ広い砂漠で➡
バイクで走る俺を
どうやって 尾行できる!?
わけねえよな｡
そんな まさか 気のせいか…｡
It's strange... Something's not right.
I feel like somebody's been tailing me all morning...
うあっ！
(ﾄﾞﾉｳﾞｧﾝ)勘のいいやつ｡
野生のコウモリにさえ
気付かれずに 近づける➡
But that can't be, can it?
この 俺様の気配を
よく感じ取ったものよ！
何だ!? てめえ！
I'm in a wide open desert... and on a motorbike.
何だって 俺をつける!?
尾行ではない！
So how could someone... follow me!
ストレイツォの情報を聞くため➡
我が軍の命令によって
貴様を拉致する！
As if, right?
ジョセフ･ジョースター！
I must be imagining things.
ス… ストレイツォだと…
我が軍だと!?
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
You're a sharp one!
I can sneak up on a wild bat without it noticing me,
and yet you somehow managed to sniff me out!
♬ 静寂の底から
Who the hell are you? And why did you follow me here?!
I wasn't just following you!
♬ 目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
My superiors are looking for dirt on Straits,
which is why they asked me to bring you in...
♬ 深紅の血潮が
...Joseph Joestar!
S-Straits?!
Your superiors?!
♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
♬ 惹きあわせる
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Leeroy Jenkins
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Leeroy Jenkins
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
♬ 握りしめて
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 12: "Pillar Man"
You bastard...
この野郎！ その顔つきと
言葉なまりは ドイツ人か！
I'm guessing from your features and accent, but... you're German?!
ドイツ軍が ストレイツォと➡
What does the German army want with Straits and old man Speedwagon?!
スピードワゴンのじいさんに
関係しているのか！
So let's fight!
かかって来な！
口を割らせて 聞き出してやる！
Maybe you'll talk if I smash your mouth open!
You wish to fight Donovan, the master of knife fighting in the German army, with your bare hands?!
ドイツ軍親衛隊のコマンドー
ドノヴァンのナイフに➡
素手で 戦おうというのか｡
侮辱を感じる｡
How insulting!
You foolish amateur!
この ド素人が！
Here, take your magic carpet back!
ほれ！ お前の乗ってきた
魔法の ボロじゅうたんだぜ！
うあ～！
ううっ…｡
A cactus?!
サ… サボテンだ！
I win!
(ﾄﾞﾉｳﾞｧﾝ)勝ちィ～！➡
俺に向かってくるなんて
10年早いぜ！
You'll need ten more years of training before you're anywhere near my level, you punk!
このハナクソが！
おい ハナクソ！
Hey, kid. Let me hear you say "You're totally right, Mr. Donovan!"
｢あなたの おっしゃるとおりです
ドノヴァンさん｣と言いな！
You're totally right, Mr. Donovan...
あ… あなたの
おっしゃるとおりです➡
ドノヴァンさん…｡
Excuse me? Can you repeat that?
何？ 聞こえないぞ？
お前の 素早い 身のこなしを見て
ぶん殴るのが めんどくせえから➡
I knew you'd be a pain to fight after watching you hop around...
...which is why I'm staying on the ground,
waiting for my chance to attack you, got it?!
こうやって 地面に
避難してるんですよ 俺は！
Huh? Waiting for your chance? To do what?
(ﾄﾞﾉｳﾞｧﾝ)何？ 避難だと？
何言ってんだ！
Eh? What's up with the cactus?
な… 何だ？ この サボテンは？
Why don't you take a closer look?
もっと よく見てみたら？
(爆発音)
(ﾄﾞﾉｳﾞｧﾝ)ドグェーッ！
ぐあ～！
ぐえっ！
俺の狙いは➡
I was getting ready to use the cactus the entire time!
初めから サボテンだったのよ！
サボテンは 95％が水分だってな！
A cactus is 95% water after all...
...which means I can easily send the Ripple through it!
波紋は 自由自在に駆け巡るぜ！
Now, start talking, Donovan!
さあ 全てを話せ ドノヴァン！
てめえが知ってること 全部だ！
You're gonna tell me everything!
《そうか… スピードワゴンの
じいさんの遺体が➡
I knew it...
When I heard that old man Speedwagon's body
was never found, I just knew...
行方不明ってんで
もしやと思っていたが…》
《あのじじい 無事だったのか｡➡
The old geezer was alive.
All right, that's great news.
そうか
そいつは いいニュースだ…》
And good news is exactly what Granny Erina needs right now!
このニュースを聞いたら
エリナばあちゃんも 喜ぶな…｡
《だが ドイツ軍のやつらに➡
Even so, who knows what those German bastards are doing to him.
どんな目に
遭わされていることやら｡➡
I'll rescue him, and hurry home...
so I can see Granny Erina's smiling face!
救い出してやる！
そして 一刻も早く➡
エリナばあちゃんの
笑顔を見るんだ！》
(ﾊﾞｲｸのｴﾝｼﾞﾝ音)
(ﾄﾞﾉｳﾞｧﾝ)わ～！ む… むごい！
S-So cruel!
(科学者１)シュトロハイム少佐！
柱に ひびが入りました！➡
Major Stroheim, the pillar is cracking!
So far it's consumed five bodies worth of blood.
柱に吸い取られている
血液量は ５人分！➡
柱の男の能力は 未知数なので➡
We'll gradually proceed until we know
how powerful the Pillar Man can be.
あまり エネルギーを与えるのは
危険と推測するからです！
Good.
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)うむ…｡
How are we extracting the blood from the prisoners?
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
どうやって 捕虜どもの血液を
搾り取っている？
お～っと！ いや 聞くまい！
Never mind, forget I asked!
I get the idea, so spare the details.
話さんでいい｡ 想像できるわ！
(うがい)
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)スピ～ドワゴ～ン！
Speedwagon...
何を怖がっている？
What's there to be afraid of?
少し おびえ方が異常じゃないか？
Don't you think you're getting a bit worked up?
You can ignore just how dangerous he is, but please reconsider!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うぬぼれ屋でも
やつを 甘く考えるな！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)なあ 聞け！
あの実験室は シェルターだ！
Listen here...
This experiment chamber is essentially a bomb shelter.
The walls are covered in twenty inch thick steel plates!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
鉄板の厚さは なんと50cm！➡
おまけに 火炎放射器 機関銃
時限爆薬まで セットされている｡
It's also equipped with flamethrowers and machine guns.
It even has a self-destruct mechanism!
Do children cower in fear at the sight of
a caged grizzly bear at the zoo?
動物園のおりの中の グリズリーを
怖がる 子供がおるか？
いな～い！
No!
I'd wager he's just a primitive man
who's been stuck in a state of hibernation for too long!
やつは 長生きしているだけの➡
しみったれた ただの
原始人にすぎないと思うよ！
この シュトロハイムは！
Something is pouring out of it!
(兵士１)何かが 噴き出したぞ！
ああっ！
It's blood!
(科学者２)
血液です！ 柱に染み込んだ血液が
噴き出しています！➡
The blood we gave to the pillar is spraying out!
何も見えません！
We can't see a thing!
Activate the showers and get a visual!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)シャワーで 洗い流せ！
(降り注ぐ水の音)
(柱の男)カッ｡
(科学者たち)あっ！
ああっ！ おお…｡
(一同)ああ…｡
フフフ…｡
His skin was like stone, but now it has
all the color and complexion of human flesh!
(科学者１)
石のような肌だったのが➡
艶々と
光沢と血色が付いています！➡
He's alive!
生き物です！
人間と変わりない 生き物です！
He's alive and looks like a regular human!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
フフ… フハハハハハ！➡
He needs a proper name.
名前が欲しいな｡ 柱の男じゃあ
いまいち 呼びにくい｡
"The Pillar Man" is a bit of a mouthful.
この シュトロハイムが
ゴッドファーザーになってやる！
And naming him will make me, the brilliant Stroheim, his godfather!
そうだな…｡
I have an idea...
メキシコに吹く熱風という意味の
サンタナというのは どうかな！
...why not name him after the hellish winds of Mexico?
I'll call him Santana!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
お～！ 起き上がるぞ！➡
Oh, he's getting up!
Now, rise...
さあ 立ってみろ！➡
Rise and show us your true power, Santana!
我々の前に 能力を見せてみろ！
サンタナ！
ん？
♬～
ブワーッハハハッ！
アハハハッ！➡
バァーッハハハッ！
アヒーッ アヒーッ！
ヒヒヒッ ヒヒヒッ！ 何だ!?
Well, isn't this guy just a riot?!
なかなか 楽しいやつじゃあないか
あのサンタナは！➡
Santana here is supposed to be the ultimate life form?!
究極の生物だと!?
なんと アヒーッ！ 究極！
Ultimate compared to who, exactly?!
見ろよ スピードワゴン！
Take a look, Speedwagon!
Look at him sniffing around in there, just like a caveman!
クンクン においを嗅ぐところなど
まるで 原始人だな！
How could he have any brains?!
知能は 低いんじゃあないのか!?
くっ…｡
笑わしてくれるぜ｡
まあいい｡
Such divine comedy!
Oh well, let's just assume he's the one
who first created the stone masks.
石仮面を作ったのは
やつとしよう！➡
おい！ 例の実験開始だ！
Hey, go start the experiment.
隣の部屋から あれを放て！
(兵士２)はっ！
Send in the specimen from the other chamber!
Sir!
W-What is that?!
な… 何だ!? あれは！
A prisoner.
捕虜よ｡
捕虜に 石仮面をかぶせたのだ！
One that has worn the stone mask.
A-A vampire?!
きゅ… 吸血鬼か！
Until a few days ago, this was a frail old man
with one foot in the grave.
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)あいつは 数日前まで
病弱で 歯もなく➡
今にも死にそうだった 老人よ！➡
And he hasn't had a single drop of blood today, so he's starving!
今日は １滴も与えていないので
血に渇いている！➡
すぐにも 攻撃する！
どうなるか 戦わせてみるのだ！
He'll attack on sight!
Let's see what happens when they battle!
(吸血鬼)WREEEEEEEYYYYY！
うっ!? 何だ!? いきなり予想外！
What?! That wasn't what I expected!
これは ただの人間ではないか！
How is he any different from a mere human?
Sir, the test subject will be devoured if we don't do something!
(科学者２)これでは 実験材料が
ひとたまりもありません！
(科学者３)
石仮面をかぶせた 捕虜の頭に
爆薬を埋め込んでいます！
We implanted a bomb in the prisoner's head before putting the stone mask on him!
爆破させますか？
シュトロハイム少佐！
Should we detonate it, Major Stroheim?!
少佐！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)よし！ 許可する！
Major!
All right, prepare to detonate!
なっ!?
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)ま… 待て！
H-Hold on!
爆破を待て！ 顎が…
と… 頭部の下顎を見ろ！➡
Stop the detonation!
His jaw... and the top of his head!
そ… それに！
あ… あの腕を… 腕も見ろ！➡
A-And now... his arms!
Look at that!
やられたと思ったら
逆に 口や腕が➡
It appeared as if Santana's body was pierced,
but it was really just the vampire's arms being absorbed by his body!
サンタナの体と 一体化している！
(吸血鬼)GUAAAA！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)やつは 一体化して
取り込んでいる！➡
He's eating him by absorbing his body...
...and swallowing him alive!
食っているんだ！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)なんという生き物！➡
What an amazing specimen!
The stone mask creates vampires for him to eat,
and then Santana uses his body to consume them!
石仮面の男は やつの食料なんだ！
サンタナは 体全体で食うんだ！➡
す… すると やつは➡
Th-That means... he can most likely absorb
the vampire's life energy by devouring them like that!
仮面の男の 全エネルギーを
取り入れることになる！
あ…｡
He ate him! He ate the stone mask vampire!
(兵士３)食いやがった…
石仮面の男を食いやがった！➡
He ate him!
食いやがった！
(兵士２)ひえ～！
そ… それに で… でかくなった！
A-And he's gotten bigger!
うろたえるな！
Calm down!
Don't forget that this chamber is completely sealed!
あの中は 密室ということを
忘れたのか！
やつは食って 一時的に
体重が増えたにすぎない！
All he did was absorb him and grew larger!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ち… 知能は…｡
H-His intelligence...
知能は どうなのだ？
...What about his intelligence?
Is he really intelligent?!
やつに 知能はあるのか？
えっ？
S... Strohei... m...
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ)
シュ… シュトロハ… イム～｡
What?! He talked?!
何!? しゃべった！
お… 俺の名を！➡
He said my name?!
He shouldn't be able to hear anything from in there!
あの中では
声は聞こえんはずなのに！
According to Donovan the Cactus Man...
《サボテン男
ドノヴァンの話だと➡
あの屋敷の 地下20ｍの所に
警戒厳重な設備室があって➡
...65 feet below that village is a high security installation.
And that's where old man Speedwagon is being held.
スピードワゴンのじいさんは
必ず そこにいる｡➡
さて
どうやって 潜り込むかだ》
But the question is, how do I get in?
(兵士１)野菜類 缶詰 肉 ハム 卵
籠の中身は 食料品だな！
Vegetables, canned goods, beef, ham, eggs...
So that's all the food you've got?!
All right, next is the body check!
(兵士２)
よ～し 次はボディーチェックだ！
Why the sad face?
(兵士１)何を嫌がっとる！ 笑顔で
ボディーのチェックを受けろ！
You should be all smiles during your body check!
笑顔で スカートをめくれ！
Now lift up those skirts and smile!
(女性たち)えっ!?
うむ｡ ヘヘ…｡
ふぅ…｡
(女性たち)うう…｡
通ってよ～し！ 次！
You may pass.
Next!
私は テキーラ酒を
持ってまいりましたの～｡
I've brought some fabulous tequila!
通ってもよろしいかしら？
So would you kindly let me pass?
おお…｡
ムホッ｡
手を上げろ！
Hands in the air!
ちょっとでも動いたら 撃つぞ！
Take one step and we'll shoot!
Eh, why? What could ever be the problem?!
えっ？ どうして？
いきなり 何なの？
(兵士２)怪しい動きだ！
(兵士１)撃て～！
You stand out like a sore thumb!
Fire!
わ～！ 撃つな！
Don't shoot!
I get it, I'll stay put!
わ… 分かった！ 動かない～！
Shit... but I guess that's the German army for ya.
くそっ！
さ… さすが ドイツ軍だぜ！
They saw right through my fabulous disguise!
よくぞ 俺の女装を見破ったな！
Are you a retard?! It was obvious!
まぬけ！ 一目で分かるわ！
気持ち悪い！
And disgusting!
お前みたいに でかくて
筋肉質の女がいるか！ スカタン！
What kind of woman is that overgrown and muscle-bound, you dumbass!
What the hell did you see when you looked in the mirror, idiot?!
客観的に 自分を見れねえのか？
バーカ！
何!?
What was that?!
フヘヘヘ…｡
波紋！
Ripple!
Tacos!
タコス！
ちくしょ～！ 自信なくすぜ｡
Damn it, I really lost my edge...
今度は 軍服だが
バレねえだろうなあ｡
Guess I'll have to settle for a military uniform... This should work nicely.
W-What happened?!
(科学者１)ど… どうなってる!?
(科学者２)わ… 分からん！
I don't know!
(兵士１)
お前 気が付かなかったのか？
Didn't you see?!
Major Stroheim, I only looked away for a moment...
(科学者３)シュトロハイム少佐➡
わ… 私は ちょ… ちょいと
目を離したんです｡
あなたも そばにいました｡
みんな そばにいました｡➡
You were there... We were all there...
でも… 誰も見ていないのです｡
But... nobody saw a thing!
飲んどる場合か！
This is no time for coffee!
It was a second at most... My eyes left him for just a brief moment...
ほ… ほんの少しの間でした｡
私が 目を離していたのは
たった 数秒だったのです｡
私の視力は 1.5です！➡
My vision is practically perfect!
でも 中で 何が起こったのか
分かりません！➡
But even I have no idea what happened!
信じられません！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ああ…｡
It's unbelievable!
(科学者３)やつは この密室から
こつ然と 消えてしまったのです！
He somehow vanished from inside a sealed chamber!
(科学者２)
壁のどこにも 破損はありません！
We haven't even found him in the film footage!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
いいか！ 落ち着いて捜すのだ！
Remain calm! Now continue the search!
どこか 我々の見えない死角に
潜んでいるに違いない！
He's probably just hiding in a blind spot!
Cut off the air to the chamber!
酸素の供給を ストップしろ！
He'll show himself once he's desperate for breath!
苦しくなって 出てくるのを
待つのだ！
(兵士２)
ただいま 記録フィルムの現像が
完了しました！
I'm back, and I've successfully recovered the film footage!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)よし 映写しろ！
(兵士２)はっ！
Great, set it up!
Yes, sir!
始めろ｡
Start it.
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
壁に向かって 走っていくぞ！
He's running towards the wall!
ま… まさか！
Th-That's impossible!
(一同)あっ！
Th-Th-That's...
あ… ああ… あれは!?➡
空気供給管に!?
あ… あんな隙間に！
...the air vent?!
He can fit?!
ほんの ４cm×20cmの
細い隙間に➡
He contorted his body to fit through
a four centimeter by two centimeter air vent?!
自分の肉体を
折り畳んで入っていった！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
《な… なんてことだ｡
関節を外したんじゃあない！➡
U-Unbelievable!
He didn't just dislocate his joints!
やつは こ… 骨格を
バラバラにして ねじり➡
He condensed his flesh and bone
to change the very shape of his body!
自分の体を 変形させたんだ！》
(一同)ああ…｡
す… すると！➡
Th-That means he's somewhere in
the ventilation system at this very moment!
やつは この建物の空気供給管の
どこかに 潜んでいる！
Earlier, the Pillar Man, Santana, said your name, Major Stroheim!
さっき 柱の男サンタナは➡
シュトロハイム少佐
あなたの名を 呼びました｡➡
He must have overheard us through the air ducts!
空気供給管を通じて
やつに聞こえたのでしょう！
They're connected to this room?!
この部屋へ 通じておるのか!?
おい貴様！ 空気供給管のそばに
立っているんじゃあない！➡
You there, get away from the air vents this instant! It's dangerous!
危険だ！
≪(物音)
(兵士３)ああ…｡
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)うわ～！
やつが！ サンタナか～！
It's him! It's Santana!
(兵士３)ほが～！
Major Stroheim...
シュトロハイム少佐
どうかしましたか～？
What the hell is going on?
It's so dark... I can't see!
暗くって 何にも見えな～い！
なぜ 明かりを消したんです～!?
Why did all the lights turn off?!
He's inside that soldier's body!
やつが
兵士の体内に 潜り込んだ！
(兵士３)みんな どこ～？
僕を独りぼっちにしないで～！
Everyone, where'd you go?!
Don't leave me all alone!
(一同)うわ～！
I don't have a clue what's happening...
(兵士３)何か知らないけど こんな
すがすがしい気分は 初めてだ！
...but I haven't felt this good in a very long time!
I can't believe it...
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)《なんてこった！
こんなやつが 外に出たら➡
If this abomination escapes the base,
it could be a major threat to the fatherland!
我々 祖国にとっても
大きな敵になる！➡
We have to kill it!
殺さなくては！ こいつは
抹殺しなくてはならん！》
This creature must be eliminated!
構わん 殺せ！ 部下の体ごと
撃って 撃って 撃ちまくれ～！
Don't hesitate, kill it!
Shoot through your brother in arms to kill the monster inside of him!
(銃声)
オー オー オー ウヒャー！
くちぐった～い！
It tickles!
(兵士４)ヒイイイーッ！
やっぱり 生きてる！
It's still alive!
It's just as we thought...
(兵士５)予想どおりだ…｡
(兵士６)マシンガンなんかで
撃っても 死なない！
Machine gun fire won't work on it!
ぐっ… ああ…｡
(兵士７)なんてやつだ…｡
I can't believe it!
Why's it pointing its finger at us?
何だ？ あの指の形は!?
何を意味するんだ!?
What is it doing?!
ま… 待て！
H-Hold on! Isn't that a pistol?!
ピストルのつもり
なんじゃあないのか！➡
It's just copying us!
俺たちのまねを
しているんじゃあないのか!?
さ… さっきも しゃべったのは
俺の名だけだ！
Now that I recall, it was just repeating my name earlier!
やつは まねをしているんだ！
意味などない ただの猿まね…｡
The thing doesn't know what it's doing,
so it mimics us just like a monkey would...
ひょ… ひょっとすると！
Which would mean...
やつの知能は低いぞ！
...it really is lacking intelligence!
猿並みの知能なら➡
If this thing is as intelligent as a monkey,
then we can use it to our benefit!
我々 人間に
やつを 利用できないわけはない！
あばァー｡
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ･兵士３)貴様らか？
俺の眠りを邪魔したのは｡
You men... are you the ones who disturbed my slumber?
しゃ… しゃべった…｡
It spoke!
知能が低いどころじゃあない｡
He clearly doesn't lack in intelligence.
や… やつは
高度の知能を持っている！
I believe he could be smarter than us!
He was able to learn our language in such a short amount of time!
この短い時間で 我々の言葉を
学習してしまったんだ！
Die.
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ･兵士３)死ね！
(兵士たち)何だ!?
(銃声)
What the-
ぐあ～！
(兵士４)ああっ！
我々が撃ち込んだ弾丸を➡
It gathered the bullets we shot at it,
then fired them back out of its finger!
指先に集めて
撃ち返してきた～！
(兵士８)おい！ じいさん危ねえ！
こっち来て 身を隠せ！
Hey, careful gramps! Come with me and hide!
やつは指先から さっきの弾丸を
全て 撃ち返すぞ！
He's about to fire all the bullets he absorbed right at us!
要らん！ お前ら
ドイツ軍の助けなど 受けるか！
No, I don't need help from the likes of the German army!
(兵士８)やれやれだ｡
Give me a break...
(兵士８)相変わらずだな｡➡
Even in a situation like this, you're still a stubborn old mule.
こんな 非常時にまで
頑固じじいだぜ｡
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)ひぃぃ～！
お… 俺には 手に負えない！
W-We're outmatched!
く… 来るな！
Stay back!
Hey you, let me see some of that hair!
おい お前！ 髪の毛もらうぜ！
ちょいとばっかし 多めにな！
I'll actually need a lot of it!
痛で～ 何をする!?
Goddammit, what are you doing?!
痛いのは ちょいとだけさ｡
It'll only hurt for a second!
何だ？ 貴様！ 上官に向かって！
How dare you handle a superior officer like this!
あ～っ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)誰だ？
Who are you?
その性格は ま… まさか！
That attitude... It can't be!
人呼んで 波紋ヘア･アタック！
This one's called "Ripple Hair Attack!"
ああ… お前は！ お前は！➡
You... It's you!
Joseph Joestar!
ジョセフ･ジョースター！
(銃声)
ぐあっ！
I'll set up a barrier!
バリアーだぜ！
(銃声)
この髪の毛 ちょいと
水分 足りないんと違う？
This hair seems a little dry to me...
You gotta take better care of your hair
if you don't want to lose it, German guy.
よ～く手入れせんと 将来はげるぜ
ドイツ軍のおっさん！
お… お前 いつの間に ここへ!?
What are you doing here?!
よう！ じいさん！
Yo, old man!
HAI… R…｡
Ha... ir...
Anyway...
ともあれだ…｡
...it looks like I got myself into a real mess.
とんだ修羅場に
巻き込まれちまったようだな｡
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ I spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
♬ Call it morning
driving through
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
♬ The music dance and sing
The music dance and sing
♬ They make
the children really ring
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
♬ Spend the day away
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
Next Episode
He's highly intelligent!
I'm terrified!
Mr. Santana, all together now!
You primitive...
He's entering my body through the wound in my leg!
Episode 13:
"Jojo vs The Ultimate Life Form"
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)すごい 知能の持ち主
ということか｡
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)俺は恐ろしい！
サンタナさん さあ ご一緒に！
(ｻﾝﾀﾅ)この 原始人が！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
俺の足の傷口から 体内に～！